Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
All the stories the man spun came true.
So the king, the nobility, and the kingdom's rich
all went to him to get him to write them stories.
But when they saw their wishes granted,
stark terror of his power seized them,
and they began to abhor him.
When the man finally died,
the people rejoiced that this wellspring of misfortune had dried up.
No one heard the echoing sound of the dead man's scornful laughter.
Did Muto get to go back to being the prince?
He defeated the Raven's Blood.
I get it, but Kyo wrote a story about Muto.
Oh, and Roo went back to being Roo, too.
I'm so glad.
Everybody looks like they're having fun.
I want to dance with them, too.
What?
Oh, so I went back to being a duck.
Right, the prince got all of his heart back.
So that means Princess Tutu's role is finished.
I've gone back to being a plain old duck.
Look here, Roo, Muto.
It looks like I wasn't able to help the prince at all.
I just watched.
Huh?
So that was a dream?
I wonder if Bakir finished his story about Muto.
What kind of story will he make it?
I wonder if I'll be in it, too.
Huh?
Is that Bakir?
You're doing research?
Yes.
Oh!
So, um...
Did you write a story about Muto?
No.
I haven't read a story about Muto.
I haven't written it yet.
Oh.
That's okay.
Then do you want to get started on it now?
The faster we help Muto, right?
It's not that everything I write comes true.
And I don't even know yet whether or not I still have the same power.
Well, that's okay. Then do you want to get started on it now? The faster we help Myuto, right?
It's not that everything I write comes true.
And I don't even know yet whether or not I still have the same power.
I'm sure it'll turn out just fine.
I mean, if you wish, I want to help Myuto really hard as you write, this time you'll succeed for sure.
I'm sorry, Fakir. When I said this time, I didn't mean the time when your father and mother were...
So, you see... I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm stupid, stupid, stupid.
Fakir said he'd write it, but I had to go get all impatient and do that.
Hello?
What?
Mr. Fakir from the ballet division, you want to check out these five books?
Yes.
Oh, and that book over there.
What?
I was asked to give it to you if you came.
To me?
Mr. Altor from the music division asked me.
I don't know him.
Oh, you know what? I thought so.
What is it?
Nothing much. It's strange, but Mr. Altor has borrowed all five of these books before.
What?
Whoa!
Altor? Who is he?
All right then, everybody. I'll pass them out in turn, so please line up.
Hey, Doug, you look like you're spacing out. I bet you were so happy you couldn't sleep last night, huh?
Huh? Happy about what?
Oh, she's always spaced out, but we'll let it go.
Because today's her long-awaited first point lesson.
Point lesson? Is it really?
Point! What every girl dreams from the day that she decides to become a ballerina.
The long four days of broken nails and painful blood blisters.
Correct!
And that's why I can't have you taking the flippant attitude that leads to talking in class. You hear me?
Yes, sir!
Now, Miss Lillier, your toe shoes.
Sir!
Finally, toe shoes.
When I'm 2-2, I can do point like it's no big deal.
But I wonder if the day will come when I can dance a pas de deux with the prince like that while I'm duck.
Miss Duck!
Yes, sir!
I am sorry, but at the moment I'm afraid I can't give you toe shoes.
Huh?
Your concentration, Miss Duck, has been lacking even more than before. As if you've even lost your eagerness.
Is it possible you've come to the conclusion that you can't do anything, and so as a result, you've decided to stop trying to move forward altogether?
Um, well, I... If I really could help Muto by myself, Akira, I wouldn't be asking you. But right now, I can't do anything.
What can I do?
I'm worried. I truly am worried. I fear your desire to marry me has caused you to be deliberately remiss about your lesson!
N-nonsense! Marrying you is too great of an honor! Duck would be afraid to even think of it!
Miss Duck, please watch everyone else's practice today!
Yes, sir!
I'm gonna die!
So this is the pain of point, huh? I wish Duck could share this!
I'm always watching. Even when Fakir's trying hard, I'm just watching. Maybe that dream was prophetic.
A guy from the music division? What's this about?
What's this about?
Shhhh!
You're late.
It took you 18 days, 7 hours and 24 minutes.
What are you talking about?
That's how long it took from the time you began to research your power until you noticed me.
Mr. Fakir.
I take it your outdoor, then? What is this about?
Assumed you hadn't read it, so I set it aside. I think you'll find it useful for when you start writing your stories.
Oh, really? And what do you know?
Huh. Everything you've been dying to know.
What?
Huh? Who was that?
I'm asking you who you are?
You're as short-tempered as everyone says you are.
But remember this.
Brute force has no power in the face of words.
You want Drosselmeyer's power because you're also aware of that truth, yes?
Drosselmeyer's power?
The power to make stories into reality.
It's splendid.
And the books that have had their endings stolen by those who wish to stop them from becoming reality.
Isn't it thrilling?
You mean they took out the endings to stop them from becoming real?
Yes.
Even though the originals are sealed away, and all we can get ahold of are the copies.
Imagine, a power so strong those endings still had to be torn out.
If you're serious about attaining that power, I wouldn't mind helping you.
But you will have to follow my every order.
And be prepared to die if you should fail.
What do you mean?
Follow my every order and be prepared to die?
What the heck are you talking about? Why should he have to do those things, huh?
I am giving him a warning.
Do not take Drosselmeyer's power lightly.
If you use it improperly, there will be hell to pay.
People may even die.
You need to be prepared for that possibility.
If you want out, I won't force you.
No. Teach me.
But Kier…
It's a wise decision.
Come to my house tomorrow.
I'll be waiting for Kier.
He is awakened.
This is dangerous.
We must take steps far.
Let us kill him.
Now, now, hold on.
It seems he's gained the knowledge, but that's all.
It wouldn't be a bad thing for us to watch for a little longer.
Nothing could be better than if this matter settled itself without mishap.
But if necessary, we'll take steps when the time comes that we need to do so.
Oh dear. They've finally begun to go into action. If they do that, the story will stop.
Not good. This is extremely bad news indeed, little duck.
Say, Fakir, I've been thinking and I've decided I'm going to help you.
Huh?
Well, because that's the only thing I can really do right now. So I'm just going to do what I can with all I've got. If there's something I can help you with, tell me, no matter what it is.
But isn't there something weird about that Autor guy? I wonder if this is okay.
Weird or not, we have no choice.
No entourage.
What? You mean me, Mr. Autor? I just…
I won't repeat myself.
Things relating to Drosselmeyer are gathered inside this house. It is a holy place.
Are you the weird Autor, Zura?
People like you two who are totally unrelated aren't allowed inside. Now, come, Fakir.
What unrelated?
Please take Uzura and go home.
Good luck, Fakir.
This is Drosselmeyer's study, perfectly recreated from the data I gathered. Paper made from ten-year-old reeds, blue and black ink at a seven-to-three ratio.
The feather of a white swan that's crossed the sea three times is best for the pen, but for this pen, I substituted a duck's feather.
So then…
What was that for?
Ritual ablutions.
They say Drosselmeyer always cleansed his body with water before he wrote his stories.
Didn't you know?
Why should I?
A direct descendant of Drosselmeyer's? And this is your level?
A direct descendant of Drosselmeyer?
Oh, no. You're not going to say you didn't know that either, are you? It's a fact about yourself. You really take the cake.
This is a Drosselmeyer family tree that I drew after my own research.
Look, Drosselmeyer is here, and here you are.
I believe I'm probably connected this way from this branch, but I don't have all the evidence yet.
But the one who helped my father when he was lost as a boy is this person written here. I know that much.
I have Drosselmeyer's blood. Does that mean those books missing their endings are things that Drosselmeyer wrote?
And the fact that I saw one of those endings is…
Fakir hasn't come back from Outdoor's house since then. I'm… I'm just waiting.
Everybody, pay attention!
Today, Miss Roo and Mr. Muto will demonstrate the art of dance partnering.
All of you, please watch Miss Roo's point work very closely.
I'm just watching again.
Roo…
That hurts!
Miss Roo, you hesitated to take my hand. Can you really say you loved me?
No way!
A breakup!
Roo, are you okay?
Miss Roo? Mr. Muto, what's wrong? Aren't you two getting…
It looks like it was too soon for Mr. Muto to get married. After all, the day may come when special marriage training is necessary.
Mr. Muto was always kind to Roo, but he's changing more and more.
Vakir! Vakir! Vakir!
Would you be quiet?
Is Vakir…
Vakir…
Vakir?
Vakir, hang on! Hang in there! What did you do to him?
Nothing.
Vakir…
It's true. He's been standing there three days, not eating, not sleeping, nothing.
Why did you make him do that?
Vakir…
Vakir.
Not doing that!
Vakir…
What did you do to try to stand this way? If he can't even endure this, he's a lost cause.
You know, you're horrible!
Vakir…
I'm fine.
Vakir...
Vakir…
Vakir?
Vakir exists..
Vakir…
midnight, you should be able to hear its voice if you have the power. That's the proof of your gift.
Incidentally, I clearly heard the tree make a sound like a faint sigh. Without the power,
someone would likely think it was just the wind. But where is the oak tree? You're quite observant.
The oak tree was felled long ago. Its roots alone are sleeping beneath this museum,
and one of the stones strewn here is the sole entrance through which the oak tree can be
contacted. Although even I had some trouble finding which stone it was. I'll tell you as a special...
I'm impressed. Just what you'd expect from a direct descendant, I guess I'll give you that.
Huh? That's the sole position from which you can hear the oak tree. But be prepared. There are also
many who have messed up the contact and gotten sucked in by the tree, ultimately losing their lives.
No way! Fakir, maybe you shouldn't after all. Weren't you the one who told me to hurry up and write?
I'm sorry, Fakir. I'm sorry. I didn't think it was this big major thing. I didn't know. I thought
it was just writing. But, but now... Midnight.
Fakir! Don't get in the way! Fakir, stop!
Hmm. Seems it was no good after all. Hey. Hey, you should just give up already and...
What you can see cannot be seen. What you can hear makes no sound. See what cannot be seen. Hear what cannot be heard.
Who are you? Submerge yourself in the bog of truth that lies far, far away.
Oh... Fakir?
Fakir?
Fakir!
This sound, a clock.
No.
This is a heartbeat.
Bakira, please, you must wake up.
Don't let the oak trees suck you in.
I...
Everything is one.
One is everything.
All stories are spun into one.
The beginning is the end.
The end is the beginning.
Bakir, answer me.
Bakir...
Please, come back.
The start is a happy accident.
The end, the fate for which it's meant.
Existence is false.
Truth is nothingness.
Yes, you're right.
I'll go to nothing.
In the end, becoming one with everything else.
I will watch over everyone in this way,
and go towards the eternal ending.
To those who accept everything, happiness.
To those who resist everything, glory.
Bakir!
To those who accept everything, happiness.
Bakir, answer me.
Let me hear your voice.
To those who resist everything, glory.
Be a pause every day.
It goes back to when you see everything.
A collapse every day you need to eat.
the
PDA in the early years.
ertenile
Kay face
And?
ial
fire
them
I couldn't do anything.
Nothing.
I heard a voice.
It was yours.
Someday the prince will become my prince alone.
What am I?
What should I do?
Should I love?
Can I love?
If so, how?
I will be loved.
Love me! Love me and me alone!
Everyone, throw away your lives and love me!
This is bad.
The stories turned tragic just as I wanted it to.
But what's good is it if they stop it before the end?
That won't do. That won't do at all!
I will not stand for that!
You repugnant filth!
Rue, were you just crying?
Of course not. What are you doing here?
Have I met you somewhere before, Zoda?
What do you mean? I've never met a girl.
Like, who are you?
Is this world under the control of Drosselmeyer's stories or not?
So you're going to cut off my hands then?
When here, I love everyone in the world and want to protect them.
But I also want to make all the world's love my own.
All you children who love stories, come gather round.
All you, all you have.
We'll be through the echo again, as we go.
We'll be a little twilневый emperate.
However, I liked listening to his heart.
I'm gonna say, like, some key things,
I'm gonna say, I can catch them later...
Yeah, absolutely.